* [Blog  
        The latest trends, analytics, and strategies for Facebook, Google, YouTube, SEO, Content, and more.](https://tuffgrowth.com/blog)
        
    * [Guides  
        Take a deep dive and get into the weeds with us! Get the step-by-step playbook on our most asked-for services.](https://tuffgrowth.com/growth-marketing-guides/)
        
    * [Spreadsheets  
        13 Ready-to-Go Growth Marketing Spreadsheets Startups Can Use to Boost Productivity](https://tuffgrowth.com/marketing-spreadsheets/)

    * [](https://tuffgrowth.com/blog)[

        Blog

        The latest trends, analytics, and strategies for Facebook, Google, YouTube, SEO, Content, and more.](https://tuffgrowth.com/blog)
    * [](https://tuffgrowth.com/growth-marketing-guides/)[

        Guides

        Take a deep dive and get into the weeds with us! Get the step-by-step playbook on our most asked-for services.](https://tuffgrowth.com/growth-marketing-guides/)
    * [](https://tuffgrowth.com/marketing-spreadsheets)[

        Spreadsheets

        13 Ready-to-Go Growth Marketing Spreadsheets Startups Can Use to Boost Productivity](https://tuffgrowth.com/marketing-spreadsheets/)

Who we are
==========

Our website address is: https://tuffgrowth.com.

What personal data we collect and why we collect it
---------------------------------------------------

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

Who we share your data with
---------------------------

How long we retain your data
----------------------------

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

What rights you have over your data
-----------------------------------

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Where we send your data
-----------------------

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Your contact information
------------------------

Additional information
----------------------

### How we protect your data

### What data breach procedures we have in place

### What third parties we receive data from

### What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data

### Industry regulatory disclosure requirements

[

](https://tuffgrowth.com/)

**Inbox:** [hello@tuffgrowth.com](mailto:hello@tuffgrowth.com)  
**Office:** 1099 Capitol St, Eagle, CO 81631

**With remote team members in:**

[

](https://www.facebook.com/tuffgrowth/) [

](https://twitter.com/Tuffgrowth)[

](https://www.linkedin.com/company/25051677/) [

](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCm6ODQnSwfvM7Gh100hFQPg/featured?view_as=subscriber)

### What We Do

### Why Tuff

### Resources

© 2024 Tuff | We're a division of Goodway Group!

This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.

### Cookie and Privacy Settings

How we use cookies

We may request cookies to be set on your device. We use cookies to let us know when you visit our websites, how you interact with us, to enrich your user experience, and to customize your relationship with our website.

Click on the different category headings to find out more. You can also change some of your preferences. Note that blocking some types of cookies may impact your experience on our websites and the services we are able to offer.

Essential Website Cookies

These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our website and to use some of its features.

Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the website, refusing them will have impact how our site functions. You always can block or delete cookies by changing your browser settings and force blocking all cookies on this website. But this will always prompt you to accept/refuse cookies when revisiting our site.

We fully respect if you want to refuse cookies but to avoid asking you again and again kindly allow us to store a cookie for that. You are free to opt out any time or opt in for other cookies to get a better experience. If you refuse cookies we will remove all set cookies in our domain.

We provide you with a list of stored cookies on your computer in our domain so you can check what we stored. Due to security reasons we are not able to show or modify cookies from other domains. You can check these in your browser security settings.

Check to enable permanent hiding of message bar and refuse all cookies if you do not opt in. We need 2 cookies to store this setting. Otherwise you will be prompted again when opening a new browser window or new a tab.

Click to enable/disable essential site cookies.

Google Analytics Cookies

These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our website is being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our website and application for you in order to enhance your experience.

If you do not want that we track your visit to our site you can disable tracking in your browser here:

Click to enable/disable Google Analytics tracking.

Other external services

We also use different external services like Google Webfonts, Google Maps, and external Video providers. Since these providers may collect personal data like your IP address we allow you to block them here. Please be aware that this might heavily reduce the functionality and appearance of our site. Changes will take effect once you reload the page.

Google Webfont Settings:

Click to enable/disable Google Webfonts.

Google Map Settings:

Click to enable/disable Google Maps.

Google reCaptcha Settings:

Click to enable/disable Google reCaptcha.

Vimeo and Youtube video embeds:

Click to enable/disable video embeds.

Other cookies

The following cookies are also needed - You can choose if you want to allow them:

Click to enable/disable \_ga - Google Analytics Cookie.

Click to enable/disable \_gid - Google Analytics Cookie.

Click to enable/disable \_gat\_\* - Google Analytics Cookie.

Privacy Policy

You can read about our cookies and privacy settings in detail on our Privacy Policy Page.
